this is the time known as the great pirate era a countless array of pirates go to battle across
the seas in search of the one piece the legendary treasure left behind by gold roger king of the
pirates monkey d luffy a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit set sail
to become the next king of the pirates as luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles they
capture the unwanted attention of the world government which will use any means necessary
to stop them can't wait to see what kind of adventures up next with a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue the crew will cover path across the grand line to the new world
after being separated from his crew luffy set out to rescue his captured brother ace
to do so he snuck into the government prison impelled down
so ace will you tell me what she said to you
she said that my brother is here
swan adamus
been a while straw boy did you miss me old pal
warden magellan strategy straw hat entrapment completed
from what we've gathered the following prisoners are assisting straw hat luffy and his infiltration of
impel impel down prisoner number eight two zero zero pirate buggy the clown prisoner number
d zero four six four former baroque works agent galdino aka mr three prisoner number c nine nine one
five former baroque works agent bentham aka mr two bon clay straw hat luffy and fawn clay are now in
district in on level three the blue godi have failed in every attempt to stop them
hey bon how do we get down to the lower levels from here
just a hop skip and a jump to the other side
by the way thanks again for sacrificing your life even if it turned out you didn't really die
oh come now there's no need to thank me
our lives are intertwined we were destined to see each other again
it looks like straw hat and bon clay are heading to the staircase to level four
it appears yes we've lost track of the other two buggy the clown and galdino report in if you see
either of them everyone on level two is rioting and straw hat still on the loose
don't know where this is headed but it sure is fun and here i thought i was gonna die of boredom
only a matter of time till they get cut what a shame
we appreciate your understanding in this matter it's fine and with that here you go your cloak
thank you for everything oh of course
and one last thing uh yes i believe there was a report of an intruder earlier is that correct yes
so it would seem but impal down is an iron tight facility so there's no escape now that we have
warden magellan on the case i can only assume that the matter will be handled very soon splendid if they
were foolish enough to sneak into the depths of hell itself it's only appropriate that they become a
permanent resident magellan's power is too terrifying to face i shudder to think i pray you have the
wisdom to run luffy what's all that doing out there well sir since the blue goddy can't seem to beat
straw hat or bon clay he took them all up to level two to try to break up the prisoner riot
why do i only find out about this now after things have gotten so out of hand there was an
earlier report but you were going gaga over hancock accusing me of negligence are you what else would
you call it you really need to take responsibility for this warden i was wondering would it be
possible to see the prisoner now sure let's go like right now warden wake up we kind of need you to
deal with this so yeah your fault and now things are completely out of control oh warden stop sighing
you'll kill us don't think i can do my job no sir you can be quite effective
oh it seems your guests have departed ah yes mistress sadie salute the commander attention
the riot is being attended to and my team is ready for a hunt hmm so what do you say
you're the woman for the job is someone stationed on level three now minotaurus is
on the prowl
that's a start but there are too many places to hide on level three it will be difficult to corner
them let's leave the riot to saw death and handle this on our own excluding saw deaths i want all
forces in the prison down on level four now yes sir of course sir right away
if minotaurus fails us and they do find the way down once they set foot on this floor
i will bury them with my own hands all those who make a mockery of this institution will suffer for
it i'll go yep still hot
i can't take it much longer the air feels like it's cooking my insides every time i breathe
i'd rather be cooked than skewered this is still the safest place to be right now
all we gotta do is figure out how to get back up to level one before we die of heat stroke
easier said than done i know i'm so dried out i don't even have a lick of spit inside my mouth
so soon i'll be just a hollowed out husk or dust in the wind
where did all the guards go it's too quiet around here they might be planning some kind of ambush
maybe we're dead maybe this is all just a dream we can't turn back now but i've got a bad feeling
we'll be irrevocable
please
Let me be honest.
This may not end well.
What is this thing?
It's a lot faster than it looks!
It's Minotaurus!
What the heck's a Minotaurus?
A cold-blooded demon guard!
A nasty beastie with the power to toss us out like yesterday's garbage!
Those are the eyes of a killer!
He's huge!
Did he eat a devil fruit or something?
How would I know?
What, are you okay?
Where did he go?
Strawboy, look out!
Wait just a-fwitty!
I-I can't breathe!
Second gear!
Gum-Gum!
Jack!
I-I can't breathe!
Second gear!
Gum-Gum!
Jack!
Hatsuko!
I'm holding you back!
You hang it in there, that looked bad.
I think I almost died.
I saw the heavenly garden of O Come My Way.
You are certainly strong, Straw Boy.
I don't think he's down for the count, but you gave that beast something to think about.
Oh?
Oh, no, no, no!
Boo, boo, boo!
You big meanie!
Have you no shame!
Cosmetics!
I need cosmetics!
Stat!
Plus some pointe shoes and some clothes and some weapons and...
Some drinks, some tears and some O Come My Way.
I think I'll pass on the tears, but I'm gonna drop if food doesn't happen soon.
Oh, don't worry your pretty little head, Straw Boy.
It's too, too easy to get down to level four from where we are now.
You'll see.
Are you serious?
Yes, but did you get the two-two joke?
I love that one!
Anyway, see that?
Just climb up this wall all the way to the top.
Just up there?
No problem.
Don't just go barging in, though.
You'll need to watch your step.
Right!
What the hell?
My hand feels like it was frying on a skillet or something!
Frying on a skillet, eh?
You're not too far off.
Is your hand okay?
One, two, jump!
Ah! Hot! Hot!
Ah!
Hey, come here.
Take a look at this.
Huh?
That is a lot of smoke!
Don't tell me we have to go down there!
It's bad enough up here on the ledge!
Alas, this is the burning hate hell you so desire to visit.
And double, alas, it lives up to its name quite accurately.
Well, damn.
So what's down there?
As I said, you weren't far off when you likened it to a hot skillet,
though it's more like a giant iron pot.
Once you go down to level four, you'll find a boiling pool of blood and a blazing sea of fire.
I hope they're cooking something awesome down there and not just prisoners.
Because this place sucks.
We can jump down to the bottom, but if we land in the wrong spot, we'll be fried in an instant.
You'll be risking your life each step you take from now on.
Bon.
Hmm?
You said there was someone you wanted to see, too, right?
So, who's down there that you'd risk your life for?
Hmm.
I've heard that he's called the Miracle Worker.
He's a true hero who deserves to be free.
And his friends call him Eva!
He's the Queen of Cumberbacher Kingdom, the pink paradise of the Grand Line.
He's the leader of the queer folk, the Queen of all Queens!
The Queen of all Queens?
Sounds like a pretty important guy!
That's awesome!
Uh-huh.
I want to see him face to face, if only for a moment, but maybe we can set him free!
Huh?
Are you crazy?
We just got rid of that thing!
Why did you leave him back to us?
And what are you two doing here?
I thought you said you were going to break out!
Not you again, damn it!
I knew you'd change your mind and come with me!
Screw you!
I hope that thing eats you alive!
We were just trying to hide when that monster king crashing into us!
Now we can't shake it!
That's where he landed!
Then you're responsible for this!
Of course you are!
I don't want to run anymore!
I should have just let myself get caught so I can lie down!
Damn stupid monster!
I'm going to run straight to my grave if I can't get rid of this thing!
If it's come to this, there's only one thing to do!
Now listen up, Straw Hat!
Do you remember the buggy ball?
The powerful and awesomely flashy weapon?
I used it back when we first met, blew up half the town, and scared the living hell out of you and your friends!
You...what?
You're choking, right?
Yeah!
Oh come on!
I'm sure you remember the buggy ball!
You saw me use it to unleash massive destruction with just a single shot!
Kaboom!
You gotta remember the kaboom!
Hold on just a minute!
I think I get it!
Maybe it puts you in a state of shock or something, and it's too traumatic for you to recall, but it's all coming back now?
Something like that!
Sorry!
Ah, I see.
Well, uh...
The, uh...
The buggy ball is this big and powerful cannonball.
I guess you could say it's kind of like my special weapon.
You know, the buggy ball named after me.
Well, all right, so nobody knows anything about it, but the point is you must have a lot of confidence in it to put your name on it!
Okay, yes, and it's just as powerful as ever, only now I made it tiny!
In fact, I happen to have one with me!
I call it the muggy ball!
Who the heck is muggy?
Either way, take this, you bastard!
My special weapon, the muggy boy!
Ah!
Whoa, that's awesome!
Nice shock, huh?
Heck, a piece of cake for the muggy ball.
Bring back any memories, Straw Hat?
Won't forget that one!
Holy crap!
What is that thing made of?
I'll turn, Straw Boy.
Hey, Three, are you sure you can't use your wax wax power down here?
In this heat, it would melt in three seconds!
That'll work, three seconds is plenty!
Fly, fly, I'm flying!
Off come my rekenpo!
Memoirs of the Winter Sky!
You ready, Straw Hat?
Kendall, look!
All right, now come, come!
Electro-file!
Ah!
Yeah, we did it!
We really did it!
We beat the monster Calthang from hell!
All right!
Let's keep it up and get to the bottom of level four!
Ah!
Hello?
Hello!
This is level four.
All of our forces are rallied together under Warden Magellan.
We're ready for anything down here.
Luffy, please.
Stay away.
For better or worse, Luffy reunites with Bucky.
But shortly after they team up, an accident sends them plummeting into level four.
The situation then becomes desperate when they find that Warden Magellan and all of Impel Down's forces were lying in wait.
On the next One Piece, all forces have gathered in the battle on level four, the burning heat hell.
I'm going to be king of the pirates!
We'll be right back.
Only one piece of paper will come up.
Who's coming in?
1.
We'll be right back.